Juice-Juice Idol Club Cody Sync!
Bye bye!
[ED].
I'm hungry
I'm home
I'm hungry.
You're right, I'm hungry.
I came for the radishes
I've come for the radishes.
How rare is this salmon?
Not in this size.
I don't think so.
Delicious.
A plate, please.
They're all asking for it.
I wonder what it is...
It's long.
Long!
It's a long time.
Please give me a plate!
[Hajime Shacho's ending]The ending of "Hajime Shacho".
We had a chance to listen to a customer's story.
Let me tell you a story about a customer.
Yes, hello.
We are the Dennou Ambassadors.
As you can see
It's really
It's just the two of us.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
I'll tell you what.
Wait.
Please.
Here you go.
Uh, here we go.
May I?
Thank you.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Tonight's cherry blossom scent system
We're here to visit you at the Japan Expo.I'm here to visit the Japan Expo site.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, I'm going to go around now.
I'm off!
Wow, what a towel!
The Buddies were there!
I'm so happy.
Wow, so many people!
Oh, my God.
Oh, is that a doll?
Oh, my gosh!
It's so exciting!
It's so beautiful!
This is amazing!
Oh! Cherry blossoms!
Cherry blossoms!
What is that? Cherry blossoms?
Thank you for your hard work.
You like them a lot? Mr. Uesan.
I've heard that a lot.
I see.
Here we go.
I'm going to get winded.
I'm going to stroke it.I wonder if I can stroke it.
I've become a kyozin
I've become a Keogin.
Did I become a Kyoujin?
I could become a Keogin with just Keogin!
I became a Keogin
I became more Kyoujin!
What kind of picture was it?
Pokemon Pokemon
It's a Pokemon
I became a Keogin
Sakurata came to my house!
He's so cute!
Thank you
He's so cute.
Can you take a picture for me?
Thank you.
See you later.
Cute.Cute
Lots of yukata
There are so many yukata!
Wow!
Amazing yukata!
Amazing.
They love it.
I'm so happy.
I can feel it in my bones.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
It's like a "wow" feeling.
It's Japan, isn't it?
That's what a penkopik is, right?
That's right.
Pen-copics.
There's a picture right there.
I got it!
Looks delicious.
I like this one better.
I want to eat.
I want some wasban.
I also want some bread oshokora.
Bread dumplings are the best.
Over there.
It looks interesting!It sounds interesting.
Gentlemen.
Maybe I'm still a slacker.
Hi! Hi!
Hi!
Hello!
Today we start our journey!
We are,
Uh, right foot.
Up on the left.
It looks like we're doing pretty well with all the customers in the seats!
That's great news!
I'm glad to hear that, because we were all really worried.
I'm glad to hear it!
To the people in Paris...
Oh, she's a good dancer!
Let's scout him out!
I hope to be able to work in Paris as a professional dancer
and become a professional dancer in Paris.
I will do my best!
That's too much of a first-time salute.
Because the early days are coming right out of Inouya, too.
Indeed.
But I've never really done it before.
Yes, well, re-calibrate.Yes, well, re-call to order.
Okay, everybody.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Messy.
What does it mean in Japanese?
It means "Ojyu.
SURUMON! LUSSON!
SAKURAZUKA46!
Hello everyone!
This is SAKURAZUKA46!
It looks like this.
Sorry, it's perfect. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Good luck at the convention!
Always be gorgeous and strong!
This one blooms like a cherry blossom!
Just Plus I need it!
Shout out! Cherry Blossom River 46!
See you soon!
I'll do my best, Frenchman.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
- I'll do my best! Can I run? Run and talk? Yes, it's fine.
I'm gonna make a huge mistake. I'm so nervous. I don't know what to do.I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous.
I'm really nervous... people are small people are small people are small
I'm so nervous. I'm gonna make so many mistakes.
- Are you looking at me? Are you looking at me? What do I do?
- Where are you? Are you seeing anything? Are you seeing anything?
I'm getting so nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Oh, it's coming out.
- It's true! I'm so happy!
Forty?
I don't have to say that.
Oh! You're doing my mouth!
Thank you!
Oh, my God!
He's got a pretty face.
He's so cute!
Nakajima, I support you all a lot!
I look forward to seeing you all again.
Mercied Continua St Neal, Sakurazaka 46, Lafras Etiejunior.
Thank you so much for today.
I look forward to seeing you all again.
Mercied Continua St Neil Sakurazaka46 Rafla Society Junior
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching!
It was super fun!
Really great lunch!
The best
Thank you so much for the food!
This is the end of France already!
It's like a festival!
Looks like a festival!
Hey, Leno.
They're here.
What is it? Galette.
Buttersugar.
What's this?
It's got cheese... cheese... cheese...
Salt.
The meal type
Sour galette.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
It's good.
How is it?
Crunchy.
Is it good?Is it good?
It's so good.
Oh, my God.
I went to the bakery.
Thank you very much.
JAPAN EXPO is over!
Thank you very much!
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
We are waiting for your comments!
Hello!
Congratulations!